number nine asks when a chair flip
occurs substituents that are cyst to one
another blank while axial substituents
blank so let's draw a chair that'll be
in equilibrium with the other chair the
leftmost carbon had that methyl that was
up so it'll stay up but it'll now be
equatorial hydroxy was up right there
and now it'll remain up but now it'll be
axial the thing that we have to
understand about the two chair confir
ations if a molecule has substituents
that are cyst to one another or trans to
one another that is not going to change
when the chair flips that is an aspect
of the molecule itself so when it is CIS
it is going to remain Cy right these two
substituents the methyl and the hydroxy
will remain cyst to one another but what
happens is that any substituent that is
axial in the other chair will be
equatorial and any substituent that was
equatorial in the other chair will
become axial